A Guide to the American Public Transportation Association Collection
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- American Public Transportation Association Collection
  - 884.265 June 1960 Questionnaire (Box Box 22)
  - 884.265 May 1963 - Rapid Transit Cars - Subcommittee On (Box Box 22)
  - 884.265 Oct.1962 - Meeting Rapid Transit Cars Subcommittee (Box Box 22)
  - 884.265 Rapid Transit Cars 11/26/62 (Box Box 22)
  - 884.265 Rapid Transit Cars (Box Box 22)
  - 884.265 Rapid Transit Subcommittee (Box Box 22)
  - 884.265 Dec.1959-Rapid Transit Cars, Subcommittee Meeting (Box Box 22)
  - 884.26 May 1962 - Circular Letters and Minutes (Box Box 22)
  - May 1962 - Mechanical Division Advisory Committee on Rail Cars (Box Box 22)
  - 884.26 May 1962-Meeting Rail Cars, Advisory Committee On (Box Box 22)
  - 884.26 June 1961-Meeting ADV. Comm. on Rail Cars (Box Box 22)
  - 884.26 Nov.1958-Meeting ADV. Committee on Rail Cars (Box Box 22)
  - 884.26 Sep. 1960-Meeting Rail Cars Committee and Subcommittee (Box Box 22)
  - 890 Public Relations '70-71 (Box Box 22)
  - Characteristics of the Urban Transit Mode (Box Box 22)
  - Mr.Somerville (Box Box 22)
  - 894.03 Public Relations (Box Box 22)
  - Minutes, Public Relations Division-Feb 1946 to date (Box Box 22)
  - Minutes, Public Relations Division Feb 1946 date (Box Box 22)
  - 890 Marketing Grants (Box Box 22)
  - 890 Marketing Grants (Box Box 22)
  - 890 Marketing Grants 1974 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 MARKETING GRANTS 1974 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 MARKETING DIVISION 1972-73 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 Marketing Division 1972-1973 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 MARKETING DIVISION 1972-1973 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 MARKETING DIVISION 1974 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 MARKETING DIVISION 1974 (Box Box 22)
  - 890 Marketing Division 1974 (Box Box 22)
  - Public Relations/Ketchum,Mcleod and Grove Inc. (Box Box 22)
  - TIRES 1967 (Box Box 22)
  - Submittal of Contractual Data (Box Box 23)
  - Equipment Specification for ACT-1 Vehicle (Box Box 23)
  - ACT1-SIMULATED DEMO (Box Box 23)
  - URBAN RAPID RAIL VEHICLE AND SYSTEM PROGRAM (Box Box 23)
  - URBAN RAPID RAIL VEHICLE AND SYSTEM PROGRAM (Box Box 23)
  - URBAN RAPID RAIL VEHICLE AND SYSTEM PROGRAM (Box Box 23)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.1 General Correspondence (Box Box 23)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.1 General Correspondence (Box Box 23)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.1 General Correspondence (Box Box 23)
  - 2.1 ACT-1 (Box Box 23)
  - 2.1 ACT-1 (Box Box 23)
  - 2.1 ACT-1 (Box Box 23)
  - 2.1 ACT-1 (Box Box 23)
  - ACT-1 PROGRAM (Box Box 23)
  - ACT-1 PROGRAM (Box Box 23)
  - SUBMITTAL OF CONTRACTUAL DATA ACT-1 PROGRAM (Box Box 23)
  - ACT-1 REPORTS (Box Box 23)
  - ACT-1 CARBODY-CRITICAL DESIGN REVIEW VOLUME 1 (Box Box 23)
  - ACT-1 CARBODY-CRITICAL DESIGN REVIEW VOLUME 2 (Box Box 23)
  - TORONTO TRANSIT COMMISSION (Box Box 24)
  - 840 1972 Rail Transit Meeting (Box Box 24)
  - 840 1971 Rail Transit Meeting (Box Box 24)
  - 618.131 METAL TOKENS (Box Box 24)
  - 815.136 ANNUAL MEETING PHOTOS (Box Box 24)
  - 1976-RAPID TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 24)
  - 1976 RAPID TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 24)
  - 1976 RAPID TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 24)
  - 1976 RAPID TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 24)
  - 1976 RAPID TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 24)
  - 834.03 REGIONAL CONFERENCES (Box Box 24)
  - TRANSIT '76 REVOLUTION NEWS (Box Box 24)
  - TRANSIT 76 ASSOCIATION (Box Box 24)
  - RAIL TRANSIT 1973-74 (Box Box 24)
  - BOOKLETS (Box Box 24)
  - '73 RAIL TRANSIT CONFERENCE-CHICAGO April 23-27 MC CORMICK INN (Box Box 24)
  - 1974 RAIL TRANSIT-SAN FRANCISCO (Box Box 24)
  - 1974 RAIL-SAN FRANCISCO (Box Box 24)
  - 840 1977 RAPID TRANSIT CONF. JUNE 28-30 - Wash. D.C. (Box Box 25)
  - 840 1977 RAPID TRANSIT CONF - JUNE 28-30 Wash DC (Box Box 25)
  - RAPID TRANSIT CONFERENCE - APR. 1-3, 1975 (Box Box 25)
  - RAPID TRANSIT CONFERENCE - APR. 1-3, 1975 (Box Box 25)
  - 1975 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1975 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1975 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1975 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1974 RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1974 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1973 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 1973 - RAIL TRANSIT MEETING (Box Box 25)
  - 900 GEORGIA (Box Box 25)
  - 900 SAN FRANCISCO (Box Box 25)
  - 900 CHICAGO (Box Box 25)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 4.0 ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 5.2 ACT - Boeing Reports ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 5.2 ACT - Boeing Reports ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS PROGRAM DC-06-0082 5.2 ACT - Boeing Reports ADVISORY BOARD (Box Box 26)
  - RESEARCH REPORTS (Box Box 26)
  - RESEARCH REPORTS (Box Box 26)
  - RESEARCH REPORTS (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS 5.3.2. DOOR OPERATIONS AND CONTROL (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS 5.3.2. DOOR OPERATIONS AND CONTROL (Box Box 26)
  - URRVS 5.3.2. DOOR OPERATIONS AND CONTROL (Box Box 26)
  - DESIGN SPECIFICATION (Box Box 26)
  - DESIGN SPECIFICATION (Box Box 26)
  - 900 CHICAGO (Box Box 27)
  - 900 CHICAGO (Box Box 27)
  - 900 PHILADELPHIA (Box Box 27)
  - 900 PHILADELPHIA (Box Box 27)
  - 900 ILLINOIS (Box Box 27)
  - 900 HAWAII (Box Box 27)
  - 900 PHILADELPHIA (Box Box 27)
  - 900 OHIO - CLEVELAND (Box Box 27)
  - 252.001 COMPUTERIZED ACCOUNTING (Box Box 28)
  - 252.042 PENSIONS (Box Box 28)
  - 252.001 COMPUTERS (Box Box 28)
  - 252.001 COMPUTERS (Box Box 28)
  - CITY X AND ENVIRONS 1980 (Box Box 28)
  - 311.1 SALE OF PROPERTY (Box Box 28)
  - 311.2 SALE OF PROPERTY (Box Box 28)
  - 311.2 SALE OF PROPERTY (Box Box 28)
  - LEASE OF PROPERTY (Box Box 28)
  - 312.11 REAL ESTATE LEASE BACK CONTRACTS (Box Box 28)
  - 315.6 PAVING (Box Box 28)
  - 340.01 TRACK STRUCTURES (Box Box 28)
  - 340.02 TRACK MILEAGE (Box Box 28)
  - TRACK MAINTENANCE AND REPAIR WORK (Box Box 28)
  - COMMITTEE ON EXCHANGE OF SPECIFICATIONS (Box Box 28)
  - COMMITTEE ON EXCHANGE OF SPECIFICATIONS (Box Box 28)
  - 340.301 PAVING AND TRACK REMOVAL (Box Box 28)
  - 340.301 ABANDONMENTS (Box Box 28)
  - 342.7 RAIL GRINDERS (Box Box 28)
  - 351.23 ROBOT OPERATORS (Box Box 28)
  - PERRY TURNSTILES (Box Box 28)
  - 355.1 BUS GARAGES (Box Box 28)
  - 355.2 OUTDOOR STORAGE OF VEHICLES (Box Box 28)
  - 359.5 PURCHASE AND STORES METHODS (Box Box 28)
  - DEMAND RESPONSIVE #523.24 (Box Box 29)
  - DEMAND RESPONSIVE TRANSPORTATION (Box Box 29)
  - #520.302 LOADING OF BUS PASSENGERS (Box Box 29)
  - #523.33 RE-ROUTING STUDIES BUS (Box Box 29)
  - #523.33 CHARTER SERVICE (Box Box 29)
  - #523.33 CHARTER SERVICE (Box Box 29)
  - #523.34 SPECIAL SERVICE (Box Box 29)
  - #523.341 SUNDAY BUS SERVICE (Box Box 29)
  - #523.343 NIGHT SERVICE MOTOR BUS (Box Box 29)
  - #523.343 NIGHT SERVICE MOTOR BUS (Box Box 29)
  - #523.392 ARMY CAPS (Box Box 29)
  - #523.393 ACCESS TO AIRPORT (Box Box 29)
  - #560.4 SIGNAL INSPECTION (Box Box 29)
  - #574 A.T.A. RADIO (Box Box 29)
  - #574 TRANSIT RADIO (Box Box 29)
  - #574.1 RADIO DISPATCHING GENERAL (Box Box 29)
  - #576.2 TELEVISION TRANS. INTERFERENCE (Box Box 29)
  - #580 ACCIDENTS (Box Box 29)
  - #580.01 SERIOUS AND FATAL ACCIDENTS (Box Box 29)
  - URRUS 5.3.4 Heating and Ventilation AC (Box Box 30)
  - HVAC SYSTEM (Box Box 30)
  - URRVS 5.3.1 CarBody (Box Box 30)
  - URRVS 5.3.1 CarBody (Box Box 30)
  - URRVS 5.3.1 CarBody (Box Box 30)
  - 038 Insurance-Gen (Box Box 31)
  - 038 Insurance-Gen (Box Box 31)
  - 038 Insurance - Gen (Box Box 31)
  - 038 Insurance - Gen (Box Box 31)
  - 900.01 New Orleans Public Service, Inc. (Box Box 31)
  - 013.163 LABOR AGREEMENTS (Box Box 31)
  - 013.163 Labor agreements (Box Box 31)
  - 013.163 LABOR AGREEMENTS (Box Box 31)
  - American Transit Association (Box Box 31)
  - Personnel-A.T.A.-Info (Box Box 31)
  - Personnel - ATA - Info (Box Box 31)
  - Marketing and Rider Motivation (Box Box 31)
  - Energy Conservation and Rationing (Box Box 31)
  - 812.6 Small Operations (Box Box 31)
  - 812.6 Small Operations (Box Box 31)
  - 812.6 Small Operations (Box Box 31)
  - 812.6 Small Operations (Box Box 31)
  - Associate Member Survey (Box Box 31)
  - Associate Member Survey (Box Box 31)
  - Associate Member Survey (Box Box 31)
  - 812.4 Committee on Committees (Box Box 31)
  - Committee on Committees (Box Box 31)
  - 812 Membership Committees (Box Box 31)
  - State and County Classification (Box Box 31)
  - 812.22 State Dots (Box Box 31)
  - 900.023 ABANDONMENTS, TROLLEY COACH (Box Box 32)
  - 900.023 ABANDONMENTS, TROLLEY COACH (Box Box 32)
  - 900.023 ABANDONMENTS, TROLLEY COACH (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 BOSTON (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 MICHIGAN (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 MARYLAND (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 LOUSIANA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 LOUISVILLE (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 KANSAS (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 CHICAGO (Box Box 32)
  - 900.013 ABANDONMENT OF BUS SERVICE (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 OHIO (Box Box 32)
  - 900.013 ABANDONED OR SOLD TRANSIT COMPANIES 1968 (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 IOWA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 OREGON (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 ARKANSAS (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 CALIFORNIA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 COLARADO (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 DELAWARE (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 FLORIDA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 GEORGIA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 HONOLULU (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 NORTH DAKOTA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 NORTH CAROLINA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 NEW YORK (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 NEW JERSEY (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 MISCELLANEOUS (Box Box 32)
  - 900.013 DISCONTINUED LINES Ohio-Ore (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TABULATIONS TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TABULATIONS TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TABULATIONS TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TABULATIONS TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 32)
  - 900.013 TRANSIT COMPANIES ABANDONMENT OF BUS SERVICE (Box Box 32)
  - 900.013 TRANSIT COMPANIES ABANDONMENT OF BUS SERVICE (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 ALABAMA (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TROLLEY COACHES-GENERAL (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TROLLEY COACHES - GENERAL (Box Box 32)
  - 900.02 TROLLEY COACHES - GENERAL (Box Box 32)
  - 843.1 RAIL TRANSIT GROUP GENERAL (Box Box 33)
  - ADV. COMM. WAYS AND STRUCT. 10-15-70 (Box Box 33)
  - RAIL TRANSIT MEET SEPT.24, 1971 (Box Box 33)
  - RAIL TRANSIT STEER COMM. OCT 16,1970 (Box Box 33)
  - RAIL TRANSIT ANNUAL MEETING (Box Box 33)
  - RAIL TRANSIT COMM. STEERING 9-11-72 (Box Box 33)
  - STEERING COMM. APRIL 23rd 1970 (Box Box 33)
  - RAIL TRANSIT GROUP SEPTEMBER 19,1969 (Box Box 33)
  - ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON OPERATIONS 4-22-70 (Box Box 33)
  - POWER AND SIGNALS - APRIL 22, 1970 (Box Box 33)
  - CAR EQUIP. AND WAYS AND STRUCT. 4-22-1970 (Box Box 33)
  - 843.1 STEERING COMMITTEE ON RAIL TRANSIT GROUP (Box Box 33)
  - ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON WAYS AND STRUCTURES (Box Box 33)
  - ADVISORY COMM. ON CAR EQUIPMENT 4-22-70 (Box Box 33)
  - Instruments Transformers (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 ASA Highway Traffic (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 Training and Licensing of Auto Mechanics (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 ASA Requirements fo Motor Vehicles (Box Box 33)
  - 844 Marketing Committee of Rail Transit Division (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 ASA Highway Traffic Standards Board (Box Box 33)
  - 844 RECORDING AND OFF THE JOB INJURIES (Box Box 33)
  - 844 RECORDING AND OFF THE JOB INJURIES (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 SAFETY STANDARDS BOARD (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 NATIONAL ELECTRICAL CODE (Box Box 33)
  - SAFETY (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 ACCIDENT STATISTICS (Box Box 33)
  - 844.1 MOTOR VEHICLE TRAFFIC ACCIDENTS (Box Box 33)
  - SAFETY STANDARDS (Box Box 33)
  - MEETINGS/AGENDAS (Box Box 33)
  - 840 CAR EQUIPMENT (Box Box 33)
  - CAR EQUIPMENT COMMITTEE (Box Box 33)
  - CAR EQUIPMENT (Box Box 33)
  - #580.2 TRANSIT ACCIDENT DEATH STATISTICS (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 TRANSIT ACCIDENT DEATH STATISTICS (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 TRANSIT ACCIDENT DEATH STATISTICS (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.201 FATAL AND SERIOUS TRANSIT VEHICLES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.2 COMPARATIVE OPERATING ACCIDENT RATES (Box Box 34)
  - #580.21 TRANSIT ACCIDENTS FILE (Box Box 34)
  - #580.21 TRANSIT ACCIDENTS FILE (Box Box 34)
  - #580.21 TRANSIT ACCIDENTS FILE (Box Box 34)
  - 011.222.11 REPLIES ON USE OF SPOTTERS IN DETECTING FARE IRREGULARITIES January 1950 (Box Box 35)
  - 011.222.11 REPLIES TO QUESTIONNAIRE CONCERNING USE OF SPOTTERS for detecting irregularities in handling fares dated January 23rd, 1950 (Box Box 35)
  - 844.1 METHOD OF RECORDING AND MEASURING ACC. EXPERIENCE PART I (Box Box 36)
  - 844.1 METHOD OF RECORDING AND MEASURING ACC. EXPERIENCE PART II (Box Box 36)
  - 844.1 LIGHTING (Box Box 36)
  - 844.1 METHOD OF RECORDING AND MEASURING ACC. EXPERIENCE 4 (Box Box 36)
  - 844.1 METHOD OF RECORDING AND MEASURING ACC. EXPERIENCE PART II (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN INSTITUTE OF PLANNERS (Box Box 36)
  - 844.1 METHOD OF RECORDING AND MEASURING ACC. EXPERIENCE PART II (Box Box 36)
  - 844.1 METHOD OF RECORDING AND MEASURING ACC. EXPERIENCE PART II (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN NATIONAL STANDARDS INSTITUTE (Box Box 36)
  - NATIONAL SAFETY COUNCIL (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN ASSOCIATION OF STATE HIGHWAY AND TRANSPORTATION OFFICIALS (Box Box 36)
  - 001 ARBA (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN NATIONAL STANDARDS INSTITUTE (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN NATIONAL STANDARDS INSTITUTE (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF CIVIL ENGINEERS (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN SOCIETY FOR TESTING MATERIAL (Box Box 36)
  - AUTOMOTIVE SAFETY FOUNDATION (Box Box 36)
  - 001 COMTO (Box Box 36)
  - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF MECHANICAL ENGINEERS (Box Box 36)
  - HIGHWAY RESEARCH BOARD STATE OF THE ART (Box Box 36)
  - HIGHWAY RESEARCH BOARD STATE OF THE ART (Box Box 36)
  - HIGHWAY RESEARCH BOARD STATE OF THE ART (Box Box 36)
  - ENO FOUNDATION FOR TRANSPORTATION INC (Box Box 36)
  - FLORIDA BUS ASSOCIATION (Box Box 36)
  - HIGHWAY RESEARCH BOARD (Box Box 36)
  - HIGHWAY RESEARCH BOARD (Box Box 36)
  - 001 TRANSIT MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS MEETING (Box Box 36)
  - STATE, COUNTY, CITY SERVICE CENTER (Box Box 36)
  - 007.1 METRIC SYSTEM (Box Box 36)
  - NATIONAL FIRE PROTECTION ASSOCIATION (Box Box 37)
  - NATIONAL GOVERNORS CONFERENCE (Box Box 37)
  - NATIONAL TRANSPORT ASSOCIATION (Box Box 37)
  - NATL. CAP PARK AND PLANNING COMMITTEE (Box Box 37)
  - NATL. COMM. ON UNIFORM TRAFFIC LAWS AND ORD> (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL U.S. CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL N.F.P.A. (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL N.F.P.A. (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL U.S. CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL U.S. CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box Box 37)
  - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON URBAN TRANSPORT (Box Box 37)
  - HIGHWAY USERS ASSOCIATION (Box Box 37)
  - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF COUNTIES (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL U.S. CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL US CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box Box 37)
  - GENERAL US CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box Box 37)
  - CHAMBER OF COMMERCE TRANSPORTATION COMMITTEE (Box Box 37)
  - 001 INTERGOVERMENTAL RELATIONS (Box Box 37)
  - CAPITAL HILL CLUB (Box Box 37)
  - CANADIAN TRANSIT ASSOCIATION (Box Box 37)
  - INTERNATIONAL UNION OF PUBLIC TRANSPORT (Box Box 37)
  - WAGES, OVERTIME AND SCHEDULED HOURS NONOPERATING PERSONNEL (Box Box 38)
  - WAGES, OVERTIME AND SCHEDULED HOURS NONOPERATING PERSONNEL (Box Box 38)
  - WAGES, OVERTIME AND SCHEDULED HOURS NONOPERATING PERSONNEL (Box Box 38)
  - WAGES, OVERTIME AND SCHEDULED HOURS NONOPERATING PERSONNEL (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.886-January 1963 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.891-August 1963 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.893-March 1964 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.898-September 1964 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.899-March 1965 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.904-October 1965 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.910-December 1966 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.911-June 1967 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.916-November 1967 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.923-May/November 1968 (Box Box 38)
  - Bulletin No.924-May 1969 (Box Box 38)
  - DATA SHEET 581 RAIL BUS TROLLEY (Box Box 38)
  - BULLETIN #904 (Box Box 38)
  - DATA SHEET 581 BUS 100% (Box Box 38)
  - 1979 Rail Transit Steering Committee Meeting MORGANTOWN (Box Box 39)
  - RAIL OPERATIONS - GENERAL (Box Box 39)
  - RAIL OPERATIONS - GENERAL (Box Box 39)
  - ELECTRICAL INSULATION FIRE CHARACTERISTIC (Box Box 39)
  - RAIL OPERATIONS (T and O) OCT 24-27, 1978 COLORADO SPRINGS (Box Box 39)
  - RAIL OPERATIONS (T and O) OCT 24-27, 1978 COLORADO SPRINGS (Box Box 39)
  - '79 MINUTES - Rail Transit Steering Committee (Box Box 39)
  - 1980 MINUTES - Rail Transit Steering Committee (Box Box 39)
  - 844.1 ASA D15 INTERPRETATIONS (Box Box 39)
  - WAYS AND STRUCTURES (Box Box 39)
  - WAYS AND STRUCTURES (Box Box 39)
  - WAYS AND STRUCTURES (Box Box 39)
  - APTA TRANSIT CAR EQUIPMENT HIERARCHY (Box Box 39)
  - RAIL TRANSIT DIVISION 1972-1973 (Box Box 39)
  - RAIL TRANSIT - MISCELLANEOUS (Box Box 39)
  - 844.1ASA RECORDING AND MEASURING MOTOR VEHICLE FLEET AND PASSENGER ACCIDENT EXPERIENCE (Box Box 39)
  - 844.1ASA RECORDING AND MEASURING MOTOR VEHICLE FLEET AND PASSENGER ACCIDENT EXPERIENCE (Box Box 39)
  - 844.1ASA RECORDING AND MEASURING MOTOR VEHICLE FLEET AND PASSENGER ACCIDENT EXPERIENCE (Box Box 39)
  - 844.1ASA RECORDING AND MEASURING MOTOR VEHICLE FLEET AND PASSENGER ACCIDENT EXPERIENCE (Box Box 39)
  - 1981 RAIL TRANSIT STEERING COMM. MEETING (Box Box 39)
  - 1981 RAIL TRANSIT STEERING COMM. MEETING (Box Box 39)
  - 1981 RAIL TRANSIT STEERING COMM. MEETING (Box Box 39)
  - 012.24 1962 SPECIAL WAGE SERVICE (Box Box 40)
  - 012.24 1963 SPECIAL WAGE SERVICE (Box Box 40)
  - 012.24 1964 SPECIAL WAGE SERVICE (Box Box 40)
  - 012.24 1966 SPECIAL WAGE SERVICE (Box Box 40)
  - 012.24 1968 SPECIAL WAGE SERVICE (Box Box 40)
  - 012.24 OPERATORS' WAGE CHANGES (Box Box 40)
  - LABOR PRACTICES AND INFORMATION (Box Box 40)
  - 012.24 EXECUTIVE CONFERENCE/SEMINAR (Box Box 40)
  - 011.222.3 CASE INTERVIEW (Box Box 40)
  - 011.312 SOCIAL SECURITY (Box Box 40)
  - 011.312.1 WORKMENS' COMPENSATION (Box Box 40)
  - WAGES AND SALARIES (Box Box 40)
  - WAGES - QUESTIONNAIRE (Box Box 40)
  - 012.2 WAGES AND WORKING CONDITIONS (Box Box 40)
  - 011.211.03 IDENTIFICATION OF TRAINMEN (Box Box 40)
  - 011.222 DISCIPLINE OF TRAINMEN (Box Box 40)
  - 003.71 LIBRARIES (Box Box 41)
  - 003.2 URBAN TRANSIT COMPANIES AS OF DEC. 31st,1964 (Box Box 41)
  - CONSUMER'S PRICE INDEX 1/23/70 to Dec 1974 (Box Box 41)
  - MONTHLY REPORTS OF CHANGES IN CONSUMER'S PRICE INDEX 1961,1962,1963,1964,1965 (Box Box 41)
  - CONSUMER'S PRICE INDEX-JAN 15,1961 003.341 (Box Box 41)
  - PURCHASING POWER OF THE CONSUMER' DOLLAR IN THE U.S. Consumer Price Index (1957-59=100) (Box Box 41)
  - ENERGY AND PUBLIC TRANSIT - A PROPOSAL (Box Box 41)
  - URBAN TRANSIT RESEARCH (Box Box 41)
  - 003.2 URBAN TRANSIT COMPANIES AS OF DEC 31, 1966 Distributed by population groups (Box Box 41)
  - CENSUS OF CANADA, 1961 (Box Box 41)
  - 001 APTA PRESS (Box Box 41)
  - DISTRIBUTION STANDARD EXAMINATIONS (Box Box 41)
  - ATA PLACEMENT INTERVIEW 011.12 (Box Box 41)
  - STANDARD EXAMINATION FOR TRANSIT EMPLOYEES 011.123 (Box Box 41)
  - MINORITY STATISTICS 1943 011.125 (Box Box 41)
  - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - SURVEY (Box Box 41)
  - TRANSIT F.E.P. CASES (Box Box 41)
  - 011.128 PERSONAL REACTION (Box Box 41)
  - NATIONAL TRANSIT SAFETY (Box Box 42)
  - MANUAL OF INSTRUCTIONS - ATA OPERATING ACCIDENT CLASSIFICATION (Box Box 42)
  - #580.231 ACCIDENT PREVENTION (Box Box 42)
  - #580.213 ACCIDENT PREVENTION (Box Box 42)
  - #580.213 ACCIDENT EXPERIENCE (Box Box 42)
  - #580.215 DATA ON TRAFFIC AND PASSENGER ACCIDENTS (Box Box 42)
  - #580.215 DATA ON TRAFFIC AND PASSENGER ACCIDENTS (Box Box 42)
  - #580.23 ANALYSIS OF PASSENGER ACCIDENTS (Box Box 42)
  - #580.24 ACCIDENT REPORT AND SUMMARY (Box Box 42)
  - 580.25 TRANSIT SAFETY - SUBWAY (Box Box 42)
  - SAFETY METHODOLOGY IN RAIL RAPID TRANSIT (Box Box 42)
  - MASS TRANSIT ACCIDENTS (Box Box 42)
  - ACCIDENT PREVENTION (Box Box 42)
  - #580.543.1 SEAR BELTS (Box Box 42)
  - #580.543.1 SEAR BELTS (Box Box 42)
  - #814.8 OPERATING SUBSIDIES-FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - #814.8 OPERATING SUBSIDIES-FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - #814.8 OPERATING SUBSIDIES-FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - #814.8 OPERATING SUBSIDIES-FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - #814.8 OPERATING SUBSIDIES-FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION COMMITTEE (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION COMM. MTG. April 5, 10:00 am - ATA (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION COMM. MTG. April 5, 10:00 am - ATA (Box Box 43)
  - FARE STABILIZATION COMM. MTG. April 5, 10:00 am - ATA (Box Box 43)
  - 812.1 Membership-General (Box Box 44)
  - 812.1 Membership-General (Box Box 44)
  - 812.1 Membership-General (Box Box 44)
  - Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - 812.1 University Memberships (Box Box 44)
  - 812.1 Membership-Management Companies (Box Box 44)
  - APTA Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - APTA Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - APTA Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - APTA Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - 811 Constitution and Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - 811 Constitution and Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - 811 Constitution and Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - 811 Constitution and Bylaws (Box Box 44)
  - 812.11 Membership Campaign (Box Box 44)
  - 812.11 Special Dues Comm. '76-77 (Box Box 44)
  - 811.122 Dues (Box Box 44)
  - 900.01 D.C. TRANSIT (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 COLORADO TRANSIT DIRECTORY (1981) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 MTA TASK FORCE REPORT (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 TRANSIT ATLAS - Bus & Taxi Service in IOWA (Aug.1981) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 ARKANSAS-GENERAL (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 COLORADO (GENERAL) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 CONNECTICUT (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 WASHINGTON METRO AREA TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 TRANSIT EQUIPMENT - MIAMI (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 MILWAUKEE TRANSPORT SERVICE (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 WISCONSIN (GENERAL) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 SEATTLE - PIERCE (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 SEATTLE METRO (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 PENNSYLVANIA Mass Transit and Economic Development (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 PORT AUTHORITY OF ALLEGHENY COUNTY (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION DIRECTOR (State of Tennessee) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 LEHIGH AND NORTH HAMPTON TRANSPORTATION (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 CUMBERLAND-DAUPHIN-HARRISBURG (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 HOUSTON TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 SAN ANTONIO TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 RHODE ISLAND (GENERAL) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 TENNESSEE (GENERAL) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 CHATTANOOGA AREA REGIONAL TRANSPORTATION AUTHORITY (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 KNOXVILLE, TN (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 MEMPHIS AREA TRANSIT AUTHORITY (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 DALLAS TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 EL PASO CITY LINES (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 CITRAN (FORT WORTH) (Box Box 45)
  - 900.01 SANTA CLARA (Box Box 46)
  - KENTUCKY (GENERAL) 900.01 (Box Box 46)
  - KENTUCKY (GENERAL) 900.01 (Box Box 46)
  - KENTUCKY (GENERAL) 900.01 (Box Box 46)
  - IOWA(GENERAL) 900.01 (Box Box 46)
  - 900.01 INDIANA (GENERAL) (Box Box 46)